Tom Hunter

Summary

Accomplished full-stack software developer with 6+ years of modern development experience.

Practiced solutionist with the ability to analyse criteria and design software that is clean, scalable, well-documented, thoroughly tested, and cyber-secure. Flexibility to adapt to new development methodologies, programming conventions, and project environments.

Comfortable with prioritizing and completing tasks while maintaining regular communication with my peers. Self-motivated, respectful, and an enthusiastic team player. Always seeking new challenges and opportunities to improve.

Work Experience

Full-Stack Software Developer @ Magentus

(Feb 2022 - Current)

Collaborated with clinical team members to develop and maintain the Charm Evolution oncology application for this global healthcare technology provider. Worked in an Agile environment using an Angular front-end, a C# .NET API, and SQL database integration. Specialised in this full-stack workflow, practiced effective collaboration, and studied cybersecurity, state, and modern coding conventions.

Software Developer @ EB Games Australia

(Jul 2021 - Dec 2021)

Agile environment developing and maintaining features EB Games' applications, focusing on their ecommerce app for ebgames.com.au. Greatly enhanced my full-stack development experience and learned a variety of new skills.

Game Designer & Developer @ National Colleges of Australia (Jan 2021 – Jul 2021)

Independently designed, developed, and published dozens of small-scale educational learning tools in Unity3D for this startup teacher aides company. Practiced design techniques, client interaction, Unity MLAPI networking, and self-management.

Education

Bachelor of Games and Interactive Environments (Soft. Tech.) from Queensland University of Technology (QUT), 2017-2020

- Minored in Advanced Software Technologies and Interaction Design.
- Achieved a GPA of 6.33 and two academic performance awards.
- Learnt a variety of software and game development skills.

References

Joel Harman

Queensland University of Technology, Tutor

ja.harman@qut.edu.au

Brendan McGill

EB Games Australia, Software Development Manager brendan.mcgill@ebgames.com

LD

EB Games Australia, Technical Lead

asherw83@gmail.com

Asher Wildeboer

Contact

tomhunter.dev@gmail.com

Skills

- Advanced knowledge of web development specialising in Angular, HTML, CSS/SCSS/LESS, and JavaScript
- Advanced knowledge of API and application development using C# and .NET
- Creating RESTful APIs
- Cybersecurity and cyber-attack knowledge and mitigation
- SQL and database integration, creating stored procedures, functions, and data update scripts
- Applied leading JS libraries and frameworks such as ReactiveForms, RxJS, NgRx, Cypress, Redux, Chart.js, Bootstrap, React, and jQuery
- Familiar with version control, agile, Atlassian (Jira and Bitbucket), code estimations, and leading meetings
- Experience using and integrating AWS and Azure cloud services
- Quality assurance, self-testing, and regression testing
- Experience applying C++, Python, Java, and developing games using Unity3D and Unreal Engine 4
- Thread control, algorithms, regex, dependency injection
- Developed apps for PC, MacOS, Linux, and Android
- Studied and applied software design, UX design, and test-driven development

Web Portfolio

Outdated – update in progress

tomhunter.dev